top of page

* Products

    * Request A Service

    * Learn About A Service

* Company

Privacy Policy
==============

Dated October 11th, 2022

​

#### Introduction

This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use Our website (Service) and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.

We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

This policy only applies to information We collect:

* On this Website.
    
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between You and this Website.
    
* When You interact with Our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

Please read this policy carefully to understand Our policies and practices regarding Your information and how We will treat it. If You do not agree with Our policies and practices, Your choice is not to use Our Website. By accessing or using this Website, You agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to this Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after We make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

#### Interpretation and Definitions

###### Interpretation

The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in the plural.

###### Definitions

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:

Service refers to the Website.

Account means a unique account created for You to access Our Service or parts of Our Service.

Affiliates include Our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint venture partners, or other companies that We control or that are under common control with Us.

Company (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to Team Cymru, 901 International Parkway, FL 32746, USA.

Cookies are small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device, or any other device by a website, containing the details of Your browsing history on that website among its many uses.

Country refers to: United States

Device means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cell phone, or a digital tablet.

Personal Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual, as defined by EU General Data Protection Act [here](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/reform/what-personal-data_en).  For the purposes of this website, Personal Data includes, but is not limited to, the following:

* a name and surname
    
* an email address such as [name.surname@company.com](mailto:name.surname@company.com)
    
* a cookie ID

Service Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service, or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used.

Usage Data refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

Website refers to Team Cymru Corporate Website, accessible from [https://www.team-cymru.com](https://www.team-cymru.com/)

You means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.

#### Collecting and Using Your Personal Data

###### Types of Data Collected

Personal Data

While using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address and records and copies of Your correspondence, if You contact Us.
    
* First name and last name
    
* Usage Data
    
* Your responses to surveys that We might ask You to complete for research purposes.

Usage Data

As You navigate through and interact with Our Website, We may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about Your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including but not limited to, information such as:

* Your Device's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address)
    
* browser type
    
* browser version
    
* the pages of Our Service that You visit
    
* the time and date of Your visit
    
* the time spent on those pages
    
* unique device identifiers
    
* diagnostic data

​

When You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to;

* the type of mobile device You use
    
* Your mobile device unique ID
    
* the IP address of Your mobile device
    
* Your mobile operating system
    
* the type of mobile Internet browser You use
    
* unique device identifiers
    
* diagnostic data

We may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You visit Our Service or when You access the Service by or through a mobile device.

The information We collect automatically is only statistical data and may not include personal information, but We may maintain it or associate it with personal information We collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps Us to improve Our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling Us to:

* Estimate Our audience size and usage patterns.
    
* Store information about Your preferences, allowing Us to customize Our Website according to Your individual interests.
    
* Speed up Your searches.
    
* Recognize You when You return to Our Website.

Tracking Technologies and Cookies

We use Cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on Our Service and store certain information. Tracking technologies used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze Our Service. The technologies We use may include:

* Cookies or Browser Cookies. A cookie is a small file placed on Your Device. You can instruct Your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. However, if You do not accept Cookies, You may not be able to use some parts of Our Service. Unless You have adjusted Your browser setting so that it will refuse Cookies, Our Service may use Cookies.
    
* Web Beacons. Certain sections of Our Service and Our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of a certain section and verifying system and server integrity).

Cookies can be "Persistent" or "Session" Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on Your personal computer or mobile device when You go offline, while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close Your web browser.  We use both Session and Persistent Cookies for the purposes set out below:

Necessary / Essential Cookies

Type: Session Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies are essential to provide You with services available through the Website and to enable You to use some of its features. They help to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts. Without these Cookies, the services that You have asked for cannot be provided, and We only use these Cookies to provide You with those services.

Cookies Policy / Notice Acceptance Cookies

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies identify if users have accepted the use of cookies on the Website.

Functionality Cookies

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies allow us to remember choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering Your login details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter Your preferences every time You use the Website.

###### Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some content or applications, including advertisements on the Website, are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about You when You use Our website. The information they collect may be associated with Your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about Your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide You with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If You have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, You should contact the responsible provider directly.

###### Use of Your Personal Data

The Company may use Personal Data including, but not limited to, the following purposes:

* To provide and maintain Our Service, including to monitor the usage of Our Service.
    
* To manage Your Account: to manage Your registration as a user of the Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered user.
    
* For the performance of a contract: the development, compliance, and undertaking of the purchase contract for the products, items or services You have purchased or of any other contract with Us through the Service.
    
* To contact You: To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application's push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products or contracted services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation.
    
* To provide You with news, changes to Our Website, and general information about other goods, services and events which We offer that are similar to those that You have already purchased or enquired about unless You have opted not to receive such information.
    
* To manage Your requests: To attend and manage Your requests to Us.
    
* For business transfers: We may use Your information to evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Data held by Us about Our Service users is among the assets transferred.
    
* For other purposes; We may use Your information for other purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of Our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve Our Service, products, services, marketing and Your experience.
    
* To fulfill any other purpose for which You provide it.
    
* In any other way We may describe when You provide the information.
    
* For any other purpose with Your consent.

We may disclose personal information that We collect or You provide as described in this privacy policy:

* With Service Providers: We may share Your personal information with Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of Our Service, to contact You.
    
* For business transfers: We may share or transfer Your personal information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of Our business to another company.
    
* With Affiliates: We may share Your information with Our Affiliates, in which case We will require those Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. 
    
* With business partners: We may share Your information with Our business partners to offer You certain products, services or promotions.
    
* With other users: when You share personal information or otherwise interact in the public areas with other users, such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside.
    
* With Your consent: We may disclose Your personal information for any other purpose with Your consent.
    
* In the good faith belief that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights or property of the Company.
    
* In the good faith belief that such action is necessary to prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service.
    
* In the good faith belief that such action is necessary to protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public.
    
* In the good faith belief that such action is necessary to protect against legal liability for the Company.
    
* To fulfill the purpose for which You provide it.
    
* For any other purpose disclosed by Us when You provide the information.

##### Disclosure of Your Personal Data Required by Law

Law enforcement

Under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

Other legal requirements

The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a legal obligation.

##### Retention of Your Personal Data

The Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with Our legal obligations (for example, if We are required to retain Your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce Our legal agreements and policies.

The Company will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

##### Transfer of Your Personal Data

Your information, including Personal Data, is processed at the Company's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located. It means that this information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of Your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those from Your jurisdiction.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such information represents Your agreement to that transfer.

The Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of Your data and other personal information.

##### Security of Your Personal Data

The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us. We have implemented measures designed to secure Your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security. Any transmission of personal information is at Your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

##### Children's Privacy

Our Service is not intended for, nor directly addresses anyone under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 16. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided Us with Personal Data, please contact Us. If We become aware that We have collected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 16 without verification of parental consent, We take steps to permanently remove that information.

If We need to rely on consent as a legal basis for processing Your information and Your country requires consent from a parent, We may require Your parent's consent before We collect and use that information.

California residents under 16 years of age may have additional rights regarding the collection and sale of their 

personal information. Please see Your State Privacy Rights for more information.

##### Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide You with choices regarding the personal information You provide to Us. We have created mechanisms to provide You with the following control over Your information:

* Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set Your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies or to alert You when cookies are being sent. If You disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
    
* Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. If You do not want Us to share Your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, You can opt-out by sending Us an email with Your request to [privacy@cymru.com](mailto:privacy@cymru.com).
    
* Promotional Offers from the Company. If You do not wish to have Your email address/contact information used by the Company to promote Our own or third parties' products or services, You can opt-out by sending Us an email stating Your request to [privacy@cymru.com](mailto:privacy@cymru.com). If We have sent You a promotional email, You may send Us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt-out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience, or other transactions.

​

Residents of certain states, such as California, Nevada, Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia, and Utah may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see Your State Privacy Rights for more information.

##### Accessing and Correcting Your Information

​

You may also send Us an email at [privacy@cymru.com](mailto:privacy@cymru.com) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that You have provided to Us. We cannot delete Your personal information except by also deleting Your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if We believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

Residents of certain states, such as California, Nevada, Colorado, Virginia, and Utah may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see Your State Privacy Rights for more information.

##### Your State Privacy Rights

State consumer privacy laws may provide their residents with additional rights regarding Our use of their personal information. To learn more about California residents' privacy rights, visit [Team Cymru Privacy Policy for California Residents](https://www.team-cymru.com/team-cymru-privacy-policy-for-california-residents).

Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia, and Utah each provide their state residents with rights to:

* Confirm whether We process their personal information.
    
* Access and delete certain personal information.
    
* Data portability.
    
* Opt-out of personal data processing for targeted advertising and sales.

Colorado, Connecticut, and Virginia also provide their state residents with rights to:

* Correct inaccuracies in their personal information, taking into account the information's nature processing purpose.
    
* Opt-out of profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects. 

To exercise any of these rights please contact Us at [privacy@cymru.com](mailto:privacy@cymru.com).

To appeal a decision regarding a consumer rights request “APPEAL PROCEDURE” at [privacy@cymru.com](mailto:privacy@cymru.com)

##### Links to Other Websites

Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third-party link, You will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. 

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

##### Contact Us

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact Us:

By email: [privacy@cymru.com](mailto:privacy@cymru.com)

By phone number: +1 847-378-3300

By mail: 901 International Parkway, Suite 350, Lake Mary, FL 32746, USA

​

PRODUCTS

COMMUNITY SERVICES

CONTACT US

tel: [+1 847-378-3300](tel:+1 847-378-3300)

FOLLOW US

SUPPORT

0900-1700 ET

1400-2200 UTC

Emergencies: +1 847-378-3301

© 2024 Team Cymru. All Rights Reserved.

bottom of page
